yeah yeah gentle ER did you subscribe
did you like and subscribe to our Paris
guys all my hair is particularly messy
today
oops copies alright so guys I should
have put not clickbait in the title so
everyone would know that it is clickbait
yeah chill periscope all right so it's
your it's your product you made it you
know your copyrighted you download
inside of a periscope just to follow
comment no it is a party um it is fake
news though there is no product it's not
a product Eddy pointed that out to me
but who knows what it is we're in the
kalbi right that's what products come
from Oh make sure you close all the
stuff for the actual secret right
definitely secret yeah it close the
secret all right guys
yeah you know it you know it
you guys are the front camera here's
some panda and various states of undress
official Subaru port today we're
officially launching with a common pedal
it's the pedal no no ref where where we
go check it out check out mark this
day forward absolutely alright so do we
have the files are they ready to go
pretty much there's some weird des
numbers you want to copy them into that
so to make the two folders make the
board in the case yeah this is a coma
pedal people here there's a j15 but no J
four five six seven eight nine ten
that's fine um we can update it later
okay does it actually work now yes the
comic pedal actually works now yeah well
and we've been driving into the correct
that is it or nearly this nice yeah we
have the correct connectors so this
connector we bought from Express and it
comes with all the pins you need also
it's like 20 bucks for five room both
sides we're gonna be printing the other
side though just cuz it fits nicer in
the case you see that black up there is
3d printed of 3d printed it's quality
you can't buy it it's not a connector
cuz look it's like one injection molded
piece with metal here
nope it's Honda only and it's also not a
product pedals will not be for sale but
the software is already open source in
the Panda repo and we're about to open
source the hardware right now let's look
it over yeah
please tell me you can buy an assembled
well not for me you can't um
so the pedal is extremely DIY and be a
little bit careful so the reason we
don't we wouldn't sell this is absolute
worst-case scenario you could get
unintended acceleration in your
meaning if this thing messes up it can
completely floor the gas pedal now a few
things neutral still works and your
brakes will always overpower your gas
I'm not 100% sure about the Honda's I
know in the Toyota if you step on the
brake it won't even accelerate is it bad
to ask if the pedal works with older
cars the pedal is completely open source
no that's certainly not bad to ask no
it's bad to ask questions about like you
know will this product actually work
with the car if you're actually
legitimately asking the question it's
just bad to ask when will Subaru be
supported that's bad window by Mazda
mx-5 2005 be supported old cars is a
good question
um so every car made after I believe
it's like 95 is is gas by wire so you'll
be able to adapt this open source pedal
and you will get it to work with all
cars so this is the closest we're
probably ever gonna come to an old car
release so let me show you guys how to
use it while Eddy prepares here's the
pedalboard guys know we're not selling
kits we are just going to release this
board look Eagle as this flip feature
now it's pretty cool nice we're gonna
release the board schematic yeah we're
gonna have schematic a PCB bomb and some
nice CSV format so you just like order
all the parts on digit key and I'll
Express maybe someone will make a macro
fab file
cool we could do that too but someone
else can do too yeah yep the files are
Eagle files use eagle so well that's
what we'll be releasing put a PDF of the
schematic down so he's a good idea yeah
so here's the pedal I just got that even
a cable so let me show you guys how you
connect your pedal so here I have a
Honda giraffe that is available for sale
at shop common oh yeah yes the pedal
will allow your car to do stop and go
so our Acura ILX can do stop and go so
you can just take this ethernet plug it
in here to your color palette snake this
up and then you'll just want to plug
this guy so yeah finally a use finally
so now your kettle is connected to the
accessory part
well the pedal doesn't work on brokes
but I assumed you meant breaks no it's
only for go yeah this is the one use
this cable stuck in there yeah that's
kind of like a clip is that way yes a
part of the youth when you get these
connectors you have to modify the clip I
guess we gotta at least release a guide
for that like it comes with this clip
but it's embedded in the case so you
can't unclip it so you just cut it off
like this so driven to navteq that is a
fake news there's not actually a product
the title was clickbait I didn't lie to
you I didn't say it wasn't click babe
but we are releasing the Kama petal oh
it's the latest in non products from
common AI it's just like the common
kneel so the common neo was not a
product
um and you say about that just snap off
this tab here so that you can pull it
out easily or you could leave it in but
then good luck getting the pedal off so
petal giraffe Aeon yeah I mean once you
have you know once you need a giraffe so
that's this is just a generic expansion
port on the giraffe that you can use for
anything so yeah the pedal is not it's
not a product oh well you need a pan
you're still gonna need you're gonna
take a panda
oh we got caliber okay caliber yes you
just plugged your panda into here do you
guys know where I can find some heroin
around your hood fusion update no I
ain't really done anything on the fusion
but this is the product this is the Kama
pedal yeah I think it'll work on all the
Honda's so you know petal is not a
product so what is the new product the
Kama pedal is a pedal interceptor it's
not a new product so the title was
clickbait um no the pulsing of the Civic
is fixed in the new version yes this
will enable stop and go uncertainly and
condos but remember that the pedal the
product thing was fake news you will not
be able to buy a coma pedal from common
AI we will be releasing it under the MIT
license in our repo with the Neo
Hardware yeah all right this is chilly
I'm gonna close that close I close the
closed now so secret no your screen size
yeah how do you buy it you can't buy it
only make the difference is build
ability you can build your very own
comic panel um no it won't work with a
neo it'll only work with a giraffe I
guess but yeah it's just a different
connector on Toyota you could certainly
modify the collar pedal for Toyota but
we already have fermer mods for the
Toyota things so there's that shipper
plus update soon TM you know we've
reverted the open pilot update oh all
the focus is fixed virtually crisp and
helped me out
I think auto focus is well it's a lot
better than was yeah we'll be we'll be
continuing to improve auto focus it
won't it won't like to do it
doing before okay yeah so here you go
call me pedal so then that just plugs
into your car right so it's an
interceptor here's the connector that
goes and the nice I'm glad you like it
yeah the source is already open source
it's in it's in yeah so you just click
that on there like this and then you
plug in the wire how do you buy the
parts we'll be releasing a list and you
combine like digit key and stuff no I'd
say a firmware modest significantly
safer than the pedal the pedal is no you
don't replace the stock gas pedal it's
an interceptor oh but yeah I mean this
is really it's really only if you want
to be DIY that's why it's just not a
frolic thing really you think you won't
be able to buy these from us but oh fast
calibration no not next release but yeah
if you want to build them if someone
wants to build them and sell them that's
on that we're not gonna stop you we you
know you know my feelings are no actual
property I think intellectual property
is a dumb ass and yeah you guys can
build your own common pedals just um you
know really be careful with these things
um can I show you what it looks like in
a car show you what it looks like in a
car right see that car that car has a
common settling why is PCM bond safer
because you're running on automotive
grade hardware I mean yeah I suppose you
could build an automotive grade no but
doesn't support anything man
but it just worth comma pedal on the
actor I like so if you do bill to come a
panel we are open sourcing this we've
tried our best with the you know giving
it a bit of safety you guys can read the
code we drive around on it but yeah
really no guarantees on this no no real
need for it acidic that's all about the
other Honda's estimated cost to build
[Music]
it's like about 20 bucks yeah I feel
pretty cheap yeah
can you daisy chain other devices over
failure tonight yes you can
oh yeah really fat you can easy change
fake you can daisy-chain all the cans
that's right thank you yeah but also
like this is the board it would also be
a great thing to just you know if you
want to put something on can yeah just a
great little board you know it has ADCs
and DACs if you want to use any of that
stuff
yeah don't use this to intercept your
steering wheel torque sensor helps my
pedals are these vaguely safe pedals are
simple the and this is better than that
but no details probably gonna take out
of hakkon oh yeah it was like an op-amp
to like to get the correct values on the
output a little can transceiver there
three three regulator a good three three
reckoned it's crazy how bad most
regulators are like their response rate
behavior change it changes the current
yes the other side we got like the same
micro as the Neo board if you have some
of those left it's the same one
different crystal just to make a little
smaller and USB a for flashing it
there's no USB well the device is
actually running it's in the back you
can't plug it in yeah it's in the back
so once it's on your pedal you can't
plug it in but you can reflash you can
reflash over can well oh yeah you can
reflash Trevor can we did write a can
bootloader which has already been pushed
you can also if you do brick your common
pedal you can use show him how Paul fits
into a finalized pedal
your petal you'll just plug it in while
holding the boot button while it's
plugged in the USB mini-b and then
you'll be able to I just run make in
that pedal directory yeah it works the
new flash of panda with petal firmware
and maybe connect the inputs I think
some of the pins are already used on
panda probably cool pedal we can't do
this in the car because this is against
the wall did you get a lot of new hires
lately or just cut positions why do you
say that oh you changed the hiring page
oh no we just thank you again and we
just hired two new people yeah yeah
we're not here yet they're not here yet
one is starting next Monday and want to
starting in two weeks and he is working
out you're working out man that's what
I'm saying no actually we're really what
we're gonna really increase hiring
where's Cass they look like alright
can they keep it up can they keep it on
the DL we're not gonna say anything
about how much or anything we got a
little investment recently we got some
monies we got we get we got money but oh
you said we could buy a form to will get
a buy for a minute my form to 3d
printers so we can start printing more
connectors yeah Eddie you're gonna hate
it
I did say goodbye violence - oh yeah so
we're not gonna announce any details of
that but we did we did come into some
big money recently so we're gonna be
seriously expanding everything
everything and them you know I've also
talked about this we're a lot like a
phone company all right we're gonna
release a new product every year better
a better you know thing for your car um
so we're very early into the EON cycle
there's a whole lot of Eon updates to
come and then like this holiday season
we do the next one right and the next
holiday season we do the next one so
what's the pedal all about the pedal
allows
gas pedal in cars that like how the
cruise control cut out at 20 miles an
hour like the Acura this is the second
time they came into money is it like we
actually came to money like I think was
the same but we actually chosen
everything recently oh oh this is our
this is our second row yet calm security
I called security definitely that's
being talking about yeah we have a lot
of plans but today all we're announcing
is the color palette yeah so one of the
plans up shortly may be simple guide and
there was some people in this life at a
party always be showing always be
showing the project I got their bill
thank guys you see that one pedal there
how much would you pay for it
pedal not included no just a comment
just to comment yeah are we using
blockchain no blockchain right houses
new awfully TNF you Eric they said ones
a new model coming out Nebu airy we got
a bid 100 that's 25 100 I hear 200 do I
hear 300 in 300 it obviously if you pay
me 300 I might even be the Jaguar CEO is
so like say they're gonna drive around
for I thought they like announced like
you can go download the way mo app right
now that's what I was waiting for now if
they were buying 20,000 Volvo's wonder
what they're doing with all of us now
was like the next step in self-driving
and then like the next do not the next
to my Jaguar 2.70 Jaguar I don't need a
lecture and you have a comma pedal yeah
but leave a boycott
sky-blue element only compare comic
panels and sky booth yeah you guys know
what's wrong with the ball ball right
you know what some of the ball the way
are they on the commenting I know you
can't buy petals they'll be open but
yeah I'll show you where you can buy you
can buy some things that work with the
panel you can buy a giraffe which has
the fake Ethernet port you need to plug
your pedal into and you can buy a pop
which can be used to reflash big jokers
huge jokers localisation no no we're
gonna talk about the pedal there's a
panda there's an injection-molded paddle
so much great kama stuff yeah good buy
one of these pedals if you want to play
[Laughter]
tell us about Rover MTG rover Magic the
Gathering heroines good yeah
vocalization
oh yeah here's my keys great name he's
gonna find this here's freshly brushed
cases yeah the inside of the case anyway
that's a lot of looks a lot of great
pain free pandas are in stock well those
ones are encased yet yeah we got a case
more because I'm showing our guy go for
a driver the pedal again maybe we'll do
that tonight you could go in the Acura a
pretty great padded for time you want to
go in the accurate I mean I can go get
the keys we can come on the Acura it's
the skull pieces
and do I write Twitter responses myself
now we hired a social media coordinator
this actually this actually isn't me
yeah Harold I know it's wrong oh the
actual gas pedal is just a potentiometer
not exactly this is like a Hall effect
sensor all rights go peace okay all
right so you guys I don't know who you
know if you don't follow us on Twitter
you got you got to follow us on Twitter
on twitter twitter twitter there's a lot
i post a picture of a lot of space check
out the space are great available on the
come and shop oh oh racing yeah we got
we got 207 i think yeah ricardo we're
actually releasing the drive on cabaña
of our race so you guys can can check
that out they retweeted our self driving
awareness to it awesome can you download
the version yeah you'll be able to
download the pedal oh can you download
it off Cabana I don't know
base station guys there's so much to
talk about but today we're talking about
the pedal base station is part of a
whole thing that we're releasing okay
someone's we got to release something
Anders and we totally about a thousand
more right yeah they're coming most
adapt icture of it being done which is
cool oh yeah we're trying a different
manufacturing partner we're trying out
circuit hub they posted a picture of it
done what don't show Mike the cost right
they just show oh this is that one
already know what I can show you that
yeah what's the can address of the pedal
forgets to a wanted one yeah we're
trying to hurt enough to change it but
like I don't think we did
yeah we should like how do you know
something about the same address still
need a station base station cheap Panda
yeah I mean we're gonna be releasing
some great crepe and O'Toole soon yeah
like all the base station stuff is
parents working on the house working
well Harold the thing the thing is
Harold's also working on your
calibration so you guys got to decide
which you want more do you want fast
calibration or do you want a base
station high or if you're talented you
want to come work here and clerk isn't
it yeah I know you want calibration
that's what we're working on guys we're
working on calculation I've a look in a
calibration yeah yeah they all want
calibration I know they want calibration
right we know what you want you guys you
know what we don't do something it's
like Oh calibrate it
no we're good on calibration calibration
is also part of localization focus
afford focus or like focus on things
chase will come all right guys oh you're
old show-off
that's nice yeah hide the other window
in the other monitor no the other window
the web browser minimize that and then
we can bring the scope he's over there
chef applause soon guys we had to pull
the open pilot release
well the Florida standout is zero I have
no idea
we have those two here's like like
eagles pretty cool now you can just like
XY what's wrong become can export your
boy but no I didn't tell it it was
purple no it's some of its gold for some
reasons but like Eagle lets you export
which is cool and I just download these
models this one's a this rj45 is an ass
man guys be careful when you build a
panel you got to get high precision
resistors check it out yeah yes we use
those on the outputs of the op amp as
well as the inputs of the ADC when
you're reading don't be seriously only
1% 1% SAR probably fine ones probably
fine
tens or not you get these point ones
they'll probably like 80 cent teachers
you do want your pedal to work just get
the high precision like this connector
we made this one we made a model of but
we bought from Aliexpress but yeah
having super ocular models is important
this will retain retail we're not
selling it guys we're just releasing it
open source because we're nice like that
someone said 200 followers yeah 300
wasn't the bid yeah do you have a 3d
scanner scanning then you import it into
fusion 360 and then you just trace it in
extruder
yeah and then you print it on your form
too because it's higher precision you're
gonna what's the bomb total it's like 20
bucks and super cheap pedals are
incredibly cheap it's a neo board really
with an op-amp on it yeah another form
factor damn Subaru here on a couch
someone bid 300 through here sold to me
scope you know oh you guys get burgers
oh yeah there should always show the
merch even though it's not for sale guys
the current bid is too under the
christmas i virtually curtain oh yes I
think it's what's my salary come zero I
get no money until we're profitable we
just rejected a verses great pan itself
every profitable for corner first
profitable quarter I get a sound I know
yeah but we're not problem well that's
why we had to get investment for us you
know but you know well we'll be
profitable we're profitable we want to
grow thou growth is important alright
you could store you know yeah if you
stored your big no one will ever find
your Bitcoin this is my bitcoins there
in the pedal you can buy the penalty
iota 1k for a forgery let's yeah we're
sure
oh so maybe please know about the pedal
but we know this actually does this is
the same microcontroller that's in a
treasure and the treasure is also open
source could get the farmer to run the
treasure from her to run on this yeah
yeah the common pedal board has a one
led but the LED is not visible through
the
other than rain or need your pillow
virtually curse I forgot you have a
civic you don't need a pedal don't don't
put a pedal on the Civic it won't work
you'll be disappointed check out our
testing rig for great panels look at
those antennas yeah those are those are
broken grab it's like a lot of mounts in
the three
and act more common power hisses power
powers are caps shut the new printers do
do things the same cap as a family oh
yeah that it's a little skinnier really
distinguished so just push this is a
different cat yeah they're different
well it has to be different because a
little on fire oh the wire comes out
yeah sunroof okay for antenna yes all
right let's go visa Skopje
let's just go back to the calm pedal
we're just talking about the palace 30
minutes 30 minutes the showing for the
pedal guys you can get this pedal oh
wait no that's right you can't buy it
that's right only free you can buy that
vacuum-powered let's hope we sell a lot
of common pedals oh wait no you can't
buy them they're just free yeah do you
make the pedal make the Toyota pedal and
the way then when you have unintended
acceleration you Toyota you can see
Toyota and get rich I didn't say that
don't do that so those brave guys
uniformed you know I've come around on
Ford who do I not like what are we
selling lots of stuff go to shop to our
colleague on AI and buyer merch we sell
yawns we sell pandas we sell giraffes we
sell t-shirts we used to sell though DS
but not anymore
ya know but it's not like on the page
just selling hardware logs we just Chris
haven't Yellin he doesn't he'll arrest
yeah if he doesn't we're gonna drive yes
and virtually Chris dude you don't have
a Toyota your apples anyone
yeah yeah yeah if you're like thank you
yeah next next product we'll send you
one
um you know we've given out was gonna
have few eons now people who
substantially helped with car parts or
with knowing quality yeah you know just
just think if the stuff would help them
how we do it why should i owners use a
PCM hack instead of a pendulum that's
not only works for all those you guys
could modify it
alright guys that's 30 minutes yeah
gotta keep these scobie's 30 minutes yes
weekly comment videos I love it